Portfolio

Mehrin Mustafa Mumu

MS in Counselling Psychology, University of Dhaka BSc. Hons in Psychology, University of Dhaka



About Me



Mehrin Mostafa, Psychologist, helps people who are dissatisfied with their lives, particularly in their relationships or their search for a partner.

Mehrin helps people who are frustrated with patterns that keep playing out in their lives and who seek meaningful and lasting change. They know an important shift needs to happen and are skeptical of generic advice. Providing mental health service with a single approach is not helpful always so my expertise areas are on Person Centered Therapy, Transactional Analysis, Cognitive Behavior Therapy, Mindfulness etc.

Education

MS in Counselling Psychology, University of Dhaka

Grade - CGPA 3.84(First Class First) Year-2019-2020

BSc. Hons in Psychology, University of Dhaka

Grade - CGPA 3.49 Year-2014-2017

HSC from BCIC College, Mirpur, Dhaka

Grade - GPA 5.00 Year-2011-2013

SSC from Shaheed Abu Taleb High School, Mirpur, Dhaka

Grade - GPA 5.00 Year-2009-2011



Achievments

- 1. Scholarship on the basis of merit position of BSc. result
- NST Fellowship 2020-21 on the MS Research
 Project. Project Title "Psychological Wellbeing and Coping
 Strategies of Forcefully Displaced Myanmar Citizens".



Work Experience

Universal College Bangladesh, Monash Pathways at UCB

Senior Psychosocial Counsellor under UCB Monash July,2022- Present

Responsibilities: Conducting one to one counselling sessions with students, pastoral counselling classes, arranging events and programs for students etc

Psychological Health and Wellness Clinic (PHWC)

Psychological Counselor (Full time) August 2020- June 2022

Responsibilities: Counselling sessions, case reporting, receiving supervision for

professional growth and administrative work, conducting webinar and workshops. I have also worked in 'Moner Jotno Mobile e" and

provided tele counselling services

BRACIED

Learning Support Facilitator, LSF. (Part time) June 2020- February 2021

Responsibilities: Provide tele counselling services to primary school teachers

regarding mental well-being.



Work Experience

Student guidance and counselling office, TSC University of Dhaka

Part time counselor Oct 2019 – Sep 2020

Responsibilities: Face to face counselling session with both male

and female students and staff of University of Dhaka, supervised by the teachers of University of Dhaka.

Dhaka University Optimistic Society (DUOS) (Voluntary Service)

Peer Counselor at Monchithi July 2020- April 2021

Responsibilities: Tele counselling sessions

National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH)

Trainee Counselling
June 2020- February 2021

Responsibilities: • Face to face session (Pre-Covid)

• Tele counselling sessions (Post-covid)



Training & Workshops

Well Being Training from a NLP Trainer, Heal Foundation

Topic: Psychological Well-being of Young Adults (6 hours) of HEAL Bangladesh Foundation.

Duration: 6 Hours

Suicide Prevention, Ghatail, Tangail

Topic: Suicide and it's prevention.

Duration: 3 Hours

Stress Management

Topic: How to manage stress personally and at workplace, webinar

Duration: 1.5 Hours

Covid Anxiety Management

Topic: Taking care of mental heath during covid and reducing anxiety, webinar

Duration: 1.5 Hours

Liberating Ourselves and Counselling others by NVC

Topic: Resolving conflicts, NVC consciousness and mindfulness.

Duration: 24 Hours



Language

English

Reading: Fluent Writting: Fluent Speaking: Fluent

Bangla

Reading: Fluent Writting: Fluent Speaking: Fluent

Hobbies

- 1. Reading
- 2. Movies
- 3. Travelling
- 4. Drawing
- 5. Music

